<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Home Mate</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="aboutus_intro">Welcome to HomeMate, your one-stop destination for all your home service needs.
        Whether it\'s fixing a leaky faucet, getting your home cleaned, or revamping your interiors,
        HomeMate is here to connect you with skilled professionals who can get the job done efficiently and reliably.
        With our user-friendly app, booking a service is as easy as a few taps on your smartphone.

        Why Choose HomeMate?

Convenience: Say goodbye to the hassle of searching for reliable service providers.
            With HomeMate, you can book a service anytime, anywhere, right from the comfort of your home.

Verified Professionals: We understand the importance of security and reliability when it comes to home services.
        That\'s why all our service providers are thoroughly background-checked and verified to ensure your safety and satisfaction.

Wide Range of Services: From plumbing and electrical work to home cleaning, painting, and carpentry,
        HomeMate offers a comprehensive range of services to cater to all your home maintenance and improvement needs.

Transparent Pricing: No hidden costs or surprises! With HomeMate, you get upfront pricing quotes for all services,
                     so you know exactly what to expect before booking.

Quality Assurance: We strive for excellence in every service we provide.
        Our professionals are skilled, experienced, and committed to delivering high-quality workmanship
        that exceeds your expectations.


Easy Payment Options:
        Pay for services hassle-free through our secure payment gateway. We accept various payment methods,
        including credit/debit cards, net banking, and digital wallets, for your convenience.

24/7 Customer Support: Have a question or need assistance? Our dedicated customer support team is
        available round-the-clock to address your queries and ensure a seamless experience.


How It Works:

Browse Services: Explore our wide range of services and choose the one that fits your needs.

Select Date &amp;amp; Time: Select your preferred date and time for the service, and we'll match you with a suitable professional.

Book Service: Confirm your booking with a few simple taps, and you're all set!

Track Service: Track the status of your service in real-time and stay updated every step of the way.

Rate &amp; Review: Once the service is completed, share your feedback to help us improve and assist other users in making informed decisions.

Download HomeMate Today!

Experience the convenience and reliability of HomeMate for all your home service needs. Download the app now and take the first step towards a hassle-free home maintenance experience. Welcome to the HomeMate family, where quality meets convenience!






    </string>

</resources>